<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo noupdate="1">
    <record id="email_template_sial_montreal_en" model="mail.template">
        <field name="name">SIAL Montreal 2026 - Follow-up EN</field>
        <field name="model_id" ref="crm.model_crm_lead"/>
        <field name="subject">Following up on our meeting at SIAL Canada — CasaFolino</field>
        <field name="email_from">{{ user.email_formatted }}</field>
        <field name="email_to">{{ object.email_from }}</field>
        <field name="body_html" type="html">
<p>Dear {{ object.partner_id.name }},</p>

<p>It was a pleasure meeting you at SIAL Canada in Montréal and discussing potential opportunities together.</p>

<p>Allow me to briefly introduce CasaFolino — an Italian family-owned company focused on structured retail and foodservice, specialised in the development and production of food products that combine perceived quality, industrial reliability, and sustainable market positioning.</p>

<p>Our approach is simple: to deliver products that perform on shelf and in kitchen — ensuring rotation, continuity, and margin — without relying on forced or unsustainable premium positioning.</p>

<p>We work across both branded and Private Label projects, with a KPI-driven mindset:<br/>
• balanced recipes designed for stability, shelf life, and consistency<br/>
• formats and packaging optimised for rotation and logistics efficiency<br/>
• pricing built for competitiveness and long-term sustainability<br/>
• reliable, scalable production processes</p>

<p>Our core product categories include:<br/>
• sweet &amp; savoury spreads<br/>
• flavoured honeys and honey-based specialties<br/>
• ready-to-cook risottos<br/>
• condiments and accessible gourmet references</p>

<p>We offer flexible formats from 28 g up to 25 kg, supporting:<br/>
• Branded retail<br/>
• Private Label<br/>
• Foodservice &amp; horeca<br/>
• Industrial &amp; co-manufacturing projects</p>

<p>All products are manufactured in Italy under certified standards:<br/>
✔️ BRC &amp; IFS<br/>
✔️ Halal &amp; Kosher<br/>
✔️ Organic options on selected references</p>

<p>We would be glad to explore a potential collaboration and better understand your priorities.</p>

<p><strong>My Export Manager, Josefina Lazzaro (in CC), will be in touch with you shortly to take care of the commercial follow-up.</strong></p>

<p>Next steps could be:<br/>
• reviewing a specific category of interest<br/>
• evaluating branded or Private Label opportunities<br/>
• developing a tailored proposal (recipe · format · price positioning)<br/>
• or scheduling a short operational call to assess feasibility and timing</p>

<p>I remain at your full disposal and look forward to your feedback.</p>

<p>Warm regards,</p>

<p><strong>Antonio Folino</strong><br/>
CEO &amp; Founder — CasaFolino S.r.l. Società Benefit<br/>
casafolino.com | Lamezia Terme (CZ), Italy</p>
        </field>
        <field name="auto_delete" eval="False"/>
    </record>
</odoo>
